Guide to the Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992 AIS.1996.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reports on Philadelphia (city and county), 1950-1982; II.
  - Technical Report #13, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Technical Report #12, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Technical Report #11, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Technical Report #10, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Technical Report #9, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Technical Report #7, Community Renewal Program, 1963
  - Technical Report #6, Community Renewal Program, 1963
  - Technical Report #5, Community Renewal Program, Undated
  - Technical Report #4, Community Renewal Program, 1962
  - Technical Report #3, Community Renewal Program, Undated
  - Technical Report #2, Community Renewal Program, Undated
  - Technical Report #1, Community Renewal Program, Undated
  - Development Programming as Applied to West Philadelphia, Technical Report #8, 1964
  - Community Renewal Program Experience in Ten Cities, 1964
  - Nine Cities, The Anatomy of Downtown Renewal, c1969
  - Independence Mall 1, Redevelopment Area Plan, 1961
  - Technical Report #11, Community Renewal Program, 1964
  - Progress Report No.1 to the Department of Housing and Urban Development on SEPACT II Demonstration Project Commuter Rail System Study Program, 1966
  - Market West, Center City Redevelopment Area, Philadelphia City Planning Commission, 1965
  - Schuylkill River Park, Center City Redevelopment Area, Philadelphia City Planning Commission, 1964
  - Improved Transportation for Southeastern Pennsylvania, 1960
  - Annual Report 1980, Redevelopment Authority
  - Annual Report 1979, Redevelopment Authority
  - Annual Report 1978, Redevelopment Authority
  - Independence Mall Urban Renewal Area Technical Report, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Marketing Report No. 3, SEPACT II- Demonstration Project, Volume III, 1966
  - Marketing Report No. 3, SEPACT II- Demonstration Project, Volume II, 1966
  - 21 Cities- A National Perspective on Center City Transformations, 1970
  - Improved Transportation for Southeastern Pennsylvania, 1960
- Reports on Pennsylvania, 1943-1984; III.
  - Municipal Authority Financing in Pennsylvania Communities, 1957 (Box 18)
  - Improved Public Transit as a Partial Solution to the Problem of Traffic Congestion in Pennsylvania, 1979
  - Public Assistance in Pennsylvania: Organization, Administration, and Policy Problems, 1951
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Human Services, 1975
  - Public Assistance Allowances Compared With the Cost of Living at a Minimum Standard of Health and Decency, 1965
  - Tuition and Required Fees and Room and Board Charges at Institutions of Higher Education in Pennsylvania, 1979-80
  - Occupational Employment in Selected Manufacturing Industries in Pennsylvania, 1974
  - Toward a Planning Base for the State Civil Service Commission, 1974
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Personnel Statistics, 1968
  - Pennsylvania Projection Series: Employment, Office of State Planning and Development, 1973
  - Annual Planning Report: Fiscal Year 1979, Pennsylvania Bureau of Employment Security, 1978
  - Interim Report of the Governor's Committee on Merger of the Departments of Welfare and Public Assistance, 1958
  - Public Recreation Manual to Guide Pennsylvania Communities in the Development of a Public Recreation Service, Undated
  - Public Welfare in Pennsylvania: A Trend Analysis 1965 to 1973, 1974
  - Update: A Report on the Activities of the Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare, 1973
  - A Selected and Annotated Survey of the Literature on Transportation Status, Structure, Characteristics, Problems, and Proposed Solutions, 1967
  - Draft Action Plan for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1972
  - Annual Report, Ohio River Valley Water Sanitation Commission, 1975
  - Interim Report, The Role of Substate Regions in Transportation Planning, Programming, and Budgeting, 1975
  - Artists in Schools, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1979-80
  - Annual Report, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1977-78
  - Annual Report, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1976-77
  - Final Report, The Role of Substate Regions in Transportation Planning, Programming, and Budgeting, 1975
  - Summary Report, The Role of Substate Regions in Transportation Planning, Programming, and Budgeting, 1975
  - Pennsylvania Planning Code, 1962
  - Leadership and Management Skills for Advisory Council Members of Pennsylvania Area Agencies on Aging, 1976
  - Cable Television in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania: Analysis and Recommendations, 1979
  - A Local Officials' Guide to Combating Drug Abuse, 1971
  - Community Recreation and Parks, 1977
  - Historic Districts in Pennsylvania, 1981
  - The Educational Challenge: It Can be Met, An Appraisal and Some Considerations of Educational Needs in Pennsylvania, Undated
  - Procedural Guide for Planning Commissions, 1959
  - Act 59 Subsidy Planner: How Our Schools Are Financed, 1977
  - Public Health Laws of Pennsylvania, 1958
  - An Analysis, Evaluation and Recommendations for the Improvement of Communication/Dissemination in the Bureau of Curriculum Services, 1977
  - Annual Report, Pennsylvania Department of Health, 1983-84
  - Annual Report, Pennsylvania Department of Health, 1982-83
  - A Master Plan for Higher Education in Pennsylvania, 1967
  - Report: Higher Education in the Commonwealth, 1957
  - A Plan for Solid Waste Management in Pennsylvania, 1970
  - Pennsylvania Municipalities Planning Code, 1972
  - Household Sewage Disposal for Rural and Suburban Areas, Undated
  - Proposed Regulation IV and Guides for Compliance with Regulation IV, Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Health Division of Air Pollution Control, 1965
  - Sewer Rentals in Pennsylvania Municipalities, 1949
  - Community Renewal, Pennsylvania Department of Community Affairs, 1969
  - Farms and New Highways: Problems and Adjustments, 1964
  - Community Renewal: Redevelopment, Rehabilitation, Conservation, 1963
  - Community Renewal: Redevelopment, Rehabilitation, Neighborhood Conservation, 1956
  - Municipalities Authorities Act of 1945, 1952 (Box 19)
  - The Municipality Authorities Act, 1952
  - The Planning Commission, Bureau of Community Planning, 1977
  - Local Fire Administration in Pennsylvania, Undated
  - Local Fire Administration in Pennsylvania, Revised Edition, 1960
  - A Recommended Procedure for Parking Surveys, 1951
  - Penn-Jersey Transportation Study, Prospectus Supplement, 1962
  - Street Maintenance, Institute of Local Government at the Graduate School of Public and International Affairs at the University of Pittsburgh, 1961
  - Highway Development: Community Organization and Social Stratification, 1965
  - Public Works Workshop Maintenance of Bituminous Surfaced Streets, 1962
  - The Local Government Interchange Protection Act: Summary of the Principal Elements, 1963
  - The Methods Used by Municipalities of Pennsylvania in Financing Sewage Disposal Systems, 1956
  - The Pennsylvania Department of Transportation and the Proposal to Transfer State Roads to Local Municipalities, 1979
  - Highway Planning and Research Work Program, Department of Transportation, 1978-79
  - 12 Year Transportation Program, Department of Transportation, 1976-88
  - Refuse Collection and Disposal Practices: A Survey of Pennsylvania Cities, 1970
  - Pennsylvania's Response to the Model Cities Program, 1974
  - Pennsylvania's Urban Program: An Interim Summary, 1969
  - A Background Report: New Communities for Pennsylvania, Bureau of Research and Program Development, 1970
  - Preliminary Draft of the Proposed Planning Code for Discussion by Pennsylvania Planning Association, Undated
  - New Towns and Cities for Pennsylvania, Governor's Science Advisory Committee Panel on New Towns and Cities, 1969
  - Statistics for Gas Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1977
  - Statistics for Gas Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1982
  - Preliminary Survey for a Comprehensive State Park System for Pennsylvania, Undated
  - Seventy-First Semi-Annual Report, The General State Authority, 1984
  - Comparison of Municipalities Planning Code (Act 247 of 1968) and Repealed Planning Laws, 1969
  - Pennsylvania Performing Artists Roster, 1979-80
  - Progress Report on Survey of Annexations by Pennsylvania Local Governments, 1940-48
  - Statistics for Gas Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1978
  - Statistics for Gas Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1980
  - Statistics for Gas Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1979
  - Manual of Regulations for Official Traffic Signs, Signals and Markings, 1943
  - The Pennsylvania Industrial Development Assistance Act, c1956
  - Annual Report, The General State Authority, 1981-82
  - Authorities- Pro and Con: Experience with Authorities in Pennsylvania, Undated
  - Highlights of the Six Years of Operation, The Pennsylvania Industrial Development Authority, Undated
  - Organizing a Municipal Authority in Pennsylvania, Undated
  - The 'Authority' in Pennsylvania: Pro and Con, 1949
  - A Task Force Report, The State Role in Urban Economic Development, 1975
  - General Information, A Question and Answer Summary of the Pennsylvania Industrial Development Authority, Undated
  - Statistics by Industry and Size of Establishment, 1970
  - Statistics by Industry and Size of Establishment, 1971
  - Statistics by Industry and Size of Establishment, 1972
  - A Proposal to the United States Department of Housing and Urban Development for the Establishment of a National Urban Transportation Center (Oversize), 1967 (Box 9)
  - A Comparison of the Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969 With the Laws Governing Coal Mining in Alabama, Colorado, Illinois, Kentucky, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Utah, Virginia, and West Virginia, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Pennsylvania Programs/Activities in Environmental Education, 1978
  - A Study of Strip and Surface Mining in Appalachia, 1966
  - The Henry Fords of Solar Energy: A Workshop for Innovators in Pennsylvania, 1975
  - Automotive Air Pollution, A Report of the Panel of Technical Advisors on Automotive Air Pollution to the Joint State Government Commission, 1963
  - Smoke Control: A Report of the Joint State Government Commission, 1951
  - Strip Mining in Pennsylvania, First Report of the Committee on Strip Mining of the Joint State Government Commission, 1945
  - A Background Report: New Communities for Pennsylvania?, 1970
  - Regional Opportunities for Energy Conservation and Fuel Conversion: A Summary of the Energy Options for Business and Local Governments Seminar, 1980
  - Statistical Benchmarks for Energy in Pennsylvania, 1974
  - The Effects of Strip Mining Upon Navigable Waters and Their Tributaries, Discussion and Selected Bibliography, 1972
  - Cost Factors in Suburban Development, 1955
  - Proceedings of the 7th Pittsburgh Sanitary Engineering Conference: Planning for Water Quality Criteria in Pennsylvania, 1967
  - Statistics for Sewer Authorities in Pennsylvania, 1982
  - 1978 Statistics for Sewer Authorities
  - 1979 Statistics for Sewer Authorities
  - 1980 Statistics for Sewer Authorities
  - Economic Analysis of Properties Severed by Interstate Highways, 1969
  - Factors that Influence Economic Development at Non-Urban Interchange Locations, 1966
  - 1975 Statistics for Selected SMSA's, Department of Commerce
  - 1978 Statistics for Manufacturing Industries by County, Industry, and by Size of Establishment
  - Statistics for Manufacturing Industries, 1977
  - Statistics for Manufacturing Industries, 1976
  - Statistics for Manufacturing Industries, 1975
  - Statistics for Manufacturing Industries, 1974
  - 1974 Statistics for Selected SMSA's, Department of Commerce
  - 1973 Statistics for Selected SMSA's, Department of Commerce
  - 1976 Statistics for Selected SMSA's, Department of Commerce
  - Pennsylvania Mass Transit Statistical Report, 1973-74
  - Pennsylvania's Response to U.S. Department of Transition Report on "Rail Service in the Midwest and Northeast Region", 1974
  - PRR + NYC Spells Economic Ruin for Pennsylvania, 1963
  - Pennsylvania Transportation Resources, 1966
  - Financing Fire Protection Services, 1981
  - Fire Protection Outside Municipal Boundaries in Pennsylvania, 1945
  - Fire Service Needs in the Commonwealth, 1977
  - The Crime Laboratory: A Manual for Police Officers, 1962
  - Pennsylvania State Police, 1962
  - A Compilation of the Laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Relating to Firemen and Fire Departments, 1974
  - A Study of Local Police Training in Pennsylvania, 1972
  - New Growth: New Jobs for Pennsylvania, 1962
  - Pennsylvania Labor Relations Board Report, 1974
  - State Highway Policies and Practices in Pennsylvania, 1958
  - Statistics for Municipal Authorities, 1967
  - A Guide to Driver Education and Highway Safety, Undated
  - The Proposed Lake Erie Ohio River Canal, c1961
  - Patterns of Communication in Pennsylvania by County, 1974
  - Natural Resources of Pennsylvania, 1968
  - A Land Use Strategy for Pennsylvania: A Fair Chance for the Faire Land of William Penn, 1975
  - A Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania: An Interim Policy Report, 1976
  - Land Resource Policies and Programs: A Resume of Land Development, Use, and Management Statuses, Regulations and Practices, 1971
  - Pure Air for PA: A Joint Study of the Extent and Nature of Air Pollution in Pennsylvania, 1961
  - A Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania, Volume 2: Technical Papers Part I, 1975
  - A Property Inventory for Pennsylvania: Proposed Methodology, 1971
  - Small Cities Community Development Grants in Pennsylvania, 1979
  - A Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania: A Final Policy Report, 1978
  - A Manual for Interchange Area Planning, 1963
  - The Penn-Lincoln Parkway, 1953
  - A Pennsylvania Report: Urban Renewal and Housing Assistance, c1972
  - A Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania, Volume 2: Technical Papers Part II, 1975
  - The Lake Erie-Ohio River Canal and Pennsylvania's Future Transport Requirements, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Juvenile Justice: Community-Based Diversion From the Court, 1976
  - Review of United States Railway Station Preliminary System Plan, 1975
  - Final Summary Report, The Pennsylvania Panel on Rural Poverty, 1971
  - Planning Powers and Procedures for Pennsylvania Communities, Local Powers for Community Improvement, Undated
  - Serving Older Persons in Pennsylvania: A Summary Report and Proposals for the State Plan on Services for Older People, 1977
  - New Communities: Systems for Planning and Evaluation, c1970
  - Local and State Planning, Manual of Pennsylvania Local and State Government, Undated
  - Pennsylvania's Recreation Plan Summary, 1976
  - Pennsylvania's Recreation Plan, 1975
  - Pennsylvania's Labor Relations Board Report, 1970-73
  - Pennsylvania's Industrial Economy: An Outline of Trends and Strategic Factors 1929-1947
  - School Laws Passed by the 1957 General Assembly and Approved by the Governor
  - Digest of School Laws Enacted by the 1955 General Assembly, 1956
  - Our Standing Among the States: A Statistical Comparison of Pennsylvania's Tax Collections and School Expenditures with Other States, 1961
  - Project 10: A Plan for Pennsylvania's Outdoor Resources, c1963
  - The Utilization of Steep Slope Areas for Public Enjoyment in Pennsylvania: A Conceptual Approach to Better Methods of Land Development, 1963
  - Our Schools Today: Public School Financial Statistics Report 1966-67, 1968
  - The Pennsylvania Human Relations Act and the Pennsylvania Fair Educational Opportunities Act, 1979
  - Contiguous Wage and Benefit History of Workers Covered by the Pennsylvania U.C. Law, Wages and Industry of Covered Workers, 1975
  - Contiguous Wage and Benefit History of Workers Covered by the Pennsylvania U.C. Law, Wages and Industry of Covered Workers, 1974
  - Report to the Special Task Force of the Appropriations Committee and the Ways and Means Committee of the House of Representatives, Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1967
  - A Limited Fiscal Study of Council Schools, Tri-State Area School Study Council, 1962-63
  - Shifts in Geographic Location of Pennsylvania Industry 1920-1955, Undated
  - Characteristics of Fluid Milk Sales in Pennsylvania, 1967
  - How Pennsylvania's Industries Rate: A Comparative Survey of Pennsylvania's Industries 1967-1972, 1974
  - Statistics for Industry Groups County and Urban Places, Pennsylvania Industrial Census Series, 1966
  - Pennsylvania Investors' Handbook, Facts and Figures, 1977-78
  - The Pennsylvania Economy Mid-Year Update: Review and Outlook, 1978
  - The Pennsylvania Economy Mid-Year Update: Review and Outlook, 1977
  - Industrial and Commercial Development Authority Law and Industrial and Commercial Revenue Bonds and Mortgages, Summary of Loans, 1978-79
  - Municipal Electric Plants in Pennsylvania, 1951
  - Floods in Pennsylvania: Frequency and Magnitude, 1960
  - Flood Discharge Records Relating to Pennsylvania Streams, 1960
  - Water Resources Development by the U.S. Army Corps Engineers in Pennsylvania, 1971
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 9 Maintenance Activities Supplement Appendices and Bibliography, 1980
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 9 Maintenance Activities, 1980
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 5 Construction Quality Control Supplement- Appendices and Bibliography, 1979
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 2 Manpower, 1979
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 4 Study of Return of Certain State Highways to Local Governments, 1979
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 3 Safety and Licensing Administration, 1979
  - The Administration of Pennsylvania's Highway Plan, Report No. 1 Organization and Structure, 1979
  - Six Year Improvement Program, Department of Highways, 1969
  - Programs and Planning for the Management of the Water Resources of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Pennsylvania's Personal Income and Population by County: Selected Years 1929-1963, 1965
  - Municipal Authorities: The Pennsylvania Experience, Department of Internal Affairs, 1962
  - Handbook on Pennsylvania School Authorities, 1962
  - Summary-Policies for Critical Environmental Areas, Pennsylvania's Environmental Policy Planning Program, 1976
  - Policies for Critical Environmental Areas, Pennsylvania Environmental Quality Board, 1976
  - Pennsylvania Highways Today and Tomorrow, Report of the Highway Planning Commission, 1950
  - Interim Disaster Recovery Financing, The Pennsylvania Experience, 1973
  - Pennsylvania Industrial Districts and Parks, Undated
  - Manpower in Pennsylvania 1940-1963, Projections to 1980 Volume Two, 1967
  - Manpower of Pennsylvania Methodological Statement Volume One, 1967
  - A Study of Four Area Agencies on Aging in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania: A Comparative Analysis and Implications, 1977
  - Program Evaluation: Food Stamps and Commodity Distribution in Rural Areas of Central Pennsylvania, 1972
  - An Annotated Bibliography of County Economic Information for Pennsylvania, 1967
  - Statistics for Selected SMSA's, Pennsylvania Industrial Census Series, 1966
  - Pennsylvania League of Cities Water and Sewer Rate Survey, 1978
  - A Program of Fire Prevention in Schools Manual for Teachers, 1951
  - Transportation and Pennsylvania's Future, Summary Report of the Governor's Committee for Transportation, 1969
  - Statistics for Electric Utilities in Pennsylvania, 1983
  - Statistics for Electric Utilities, 1980
  - Statistics for Electric Utilities, 1979
  - Statistics for Electric Utilities, 1978
  - Statistics for Electric Utilities, 1977
  - Public Transportation in Pennsylvania: A Statewide Program, 1965
  - Transportation Policies for Pennsylvania, 1970
  - Pennsylvania's Future: Issues and Choices Volume II, 1978
  - Pennsylvania's Future: Issues and Choices Volume I, 1978
  - Pennsylvania Industrial Directory, 1970
  - Financing Education in Pennsylvania: A Series of Research Reports, Appendix II to Final Report, 1961
  - Pennsylvania's Recreation Plan 1980-1985, 1981
  - An Assessment of the Pennsylvania School Subsidy System, 1977
  - Guide to Programs, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1979-80
  - Guide to Programs, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1980-81
  - Guide to Programs, Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1982-83
  - Collective Bargaining and Arbitration Awards in Pennsylvania Cities, 1973
  - Collective Bargaining in Pennsylvania Local Governments, 1969
  - Proceedings on Local Government Conference on Refuse Disposal Methods, 1954 (Box 7)
  - The Socio-Economic Impacts of the Three Mile Island Incident, 1980
  - Flood Plain Information for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Uniform Region 10, 1974
- Reports on Pittsburgh (city), 1910-1985; IV.
  - Department of City Planning, 1913-1980; 1.
    - Allegheny Center proposed Redevelopment Area Plan of Redevelopment Area No. 12, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - An Administrative Study, American Society of Planning Officials, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - An Application to the Housing and Home Finance Agency for a Community Renewal Program Grant, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1947 - 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1951- 1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Basic Conditions of the Allegheny General Study Area, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Basic Conditions of the Clifton Park Study Area, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Basic Conditions of The Southwest Allegheny study area, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Bluff Street Redevelopment Area Plan: Redevelopment Area No. 6, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Chateau Street West (Preliminary) Redevelopment Area Plan, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Community Renewal Program Supplement Report, A City Rebuilds, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - A Critical Review of Form, Features and Feasibilities of The Prodigious City, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - CRP Progress Report #7, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - East Street Valley Highway Study, A Staff Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Employment Income and Population submodels, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Evaluation of Community organization activities as part of the Community Renewal Program (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Fire Station Study, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Golden Triangle Street Program, 1968-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Industrial Survey Questionnaires, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - A long Range Comprehensive Plan for the Renew and Development of Pittsburgh, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Lower North Side Redevelopment Area Plan for NO. 22, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Pittsburgh Groundwork and Inventory for the master plan, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - A Plan and Program for Commercial Development in Pittsburgh, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Planning Goals and Development Policies, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Public Property Planning Procedures, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Redevelopment Area Plan for Redevelopment area No. 3 Lower Hill District, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Report to the City Council of Pittsburgh on the inter-district traffic circuit, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 6)